aoi hoshi ni senritsu ga hashiru
a
o
i
ho
shi
ni
se
n
ri
tsu
ga
ha
shi
ru
A shudder runs over the blue planet
푸른 지구에 전율이 흐른다
kuroi arashi chikazuku toki
ku
ro
i
a
ra
shi
chi
ka
zu
ku
to
ki
It's the time the dark storm approaches
검은 폭풍이 닥쳐오는 순간
kokoro no oku de mezameru HERO
ko
ro
no
o
ku
de
me
za
ru
HE
RO
It's as if a hero is awakening on the inside
마음 속의 눈을 뜬 영웅들이여
tobitatsu no da furimukazu ni
to
bi
ta
tsu
no
da
fu
ri
mu
ka
zu
ni
Fly away and don't look back!
뒤돌아보지 말고 날아가라
DAGWON kagayake DAGWON
DA
G
WON
ka
ga
ya
ke
DA
G
WON
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Brave Command Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Dagwon... Shine on!! Dagwon!
다그온 빛나라!! 다그온
heiwa mamoru namae sa
he
i
wa
ma
mo
ru
na
ma
e
sa
The name that protects the peace
평화를 지키는 이름이다
DAGWON oretachi DAGWON
DA
G
WON
o
re
ta
chi
DA
G
WON
Dagwon! We are Dagwon!
다그온 우리는 다그온
yume wa zettai watasanai
yu
me
wa
ze
t
ta
i
wa
ta
sa
na
i
We will never hand over our dream
꿈은 절대로 넘겨줄 수 없다
afureru yuuki te ni shitai nara
a
fu
re
ru
yu
u
ki
te
ni
shi
ta
i
na
ra
To grab the overflowing courage
넘쳐흐르는 용기를 거머쥐고 싶다면
tsuyoku tsuyoku yuujou shinjiru koto sa
tsu
yo
ku
tsu
yo
ku
yu
u
jo
shi
n
ji
ru
ko
to
sa
We believe in our friendship firmly
우리 우정을 굳게 믿는 거다
kizutsuku koto mo osore wa shinai
ki
zu
tsu
ku
ko
to
mo
o
so
re
wa
shi
na
i
We are not afraid of getting hurt
상처입는 것도 두렵지 않아
mugendai no mirai wo egaku sono tame ni
mu
ge
n
da
i
no
mi
ra
i
wo
e
ga
ku
so
no
ta
me
ni
In order to reach that infinite future!
무한대의 미래를 그려내기 위해서라면
Dag Base was on the verge of destruction by the attack of the Warugaia Brothers, but it was saved thanks to Brave Seijin.
와르가이아 형제에게 파괴당할 뻔한 다그 베이스는 브레이브 성인의 출현에 의해 위기 일발로 구해졌다
Hido was taken down, but Brave Seijin was killed.
하지만 히도를 쓰러뜨리기는 했지만 브레이브 성인은 순직
And Maria finally realized the true identity of Fire En.
그리고 마리아는 마침내 파이어 엔의 정체를 알고 말았다
Rest in peace, my brother, Hido.
편히 잠들거라
내 동생 히도여…
Brother, what're you going to do?!
형, 어떻게 할 거야?!
I feel like I must defeat all of Dagwon at once!
난 지금 당장이라도 다그온 놈들을 전부 죽여버려야 성이 찰 것 같다구
-I feel the same.
-Then...!
-나도 같은 기분이야
-그럼…!
Let's finish this at once.
이렇게 되면 단숨에 끝장을 내주마
Sargasso activate! Target the Earth!
사르갓소 기동!
목표는 지구다!
To Space, our Brave Heroes
용자들 우주로
Bomb Alien Bomber Seijin
Appears
폭탄 우주인 봄버 성인
등장
We absolutely must not allow any more of the Warugaia Brothers to attack the Earth.
이 이상 와르가이아 형제의 지구 공격을 절대로 허용해선 안돼
Since Brave Seijin was done for too...
브레이브 성인도 당했으니 말이지
Now we have to end this all by ourselves.
이젠 남은 우리가 어떻게든 해야 한단 말인가
Then we have only one choice.
그렇다면 선택은 하나 뿐
We will raid and attack them!
이쪽에서 쳐들어가 녀석들을 공격한다
Agreed! Let's go to Space using Dag Base and head to Sargasso!
찬성입니다 다그 베이스로 우주에 나가서 사르갓소로 향합시다
Wait! That's too dangerous! Kai!
기다려!
그건 너무 위험해 카이…
Yes. I know.
그래… 알고 있어
카이… 그래… 알고 있어
However, it's not like we have any other choice now.
하지만… 이렇게 된 이상 달리 방법이 없잖아
Mado!
마도!
Dagwon gentlemen!
다그온 제군
마도! 다그온 제군
We will go for the final attack with Sargasso!
우리는 지금부터 사르갓소와 함께 최종 공격을 거행할 것이다
Final attack?!
최종 공격?!
We will land Sargasso on Earth and go for an all-out attack.
우리는 사르갓소를 지구에 착륙시켜 총공격에 들아갈 것이다
You will pay for killing my brother with the lives of the earthlings, and especially with your Dagwon lives!
동생을 죽인 대가는 전 지구인과 네놈들 다그온의 목숨으로 받겠다
Just wait and prepare for death.
죽을 채비하고 기다리거라
You gentlemens' lives will soon be over!
제군의 목숨도 이제 곧 끝이다!
Now we have no choice at all.
이젠 잠시도 망설일 수 없게 되었군
We will launch Dag Base to Space tomorrow morning.
우리는 내일 아침 우주를 향해 다그 베이스를 발신시킨다
Kai!
카이!
As Luna said, this battle will be dangerous, unlike the battles until now.
루나 말대로 이번 싸움은 지금까지와는 다른 위험한 싸움이 되겠지
We don't know if we will be able to come back.
살아 돌아온다는 보장도 없어
Therefore, I will let each of you decide whether to join this operation.
따라서 이 작전의 참가는 각자 판단에 맡기겠다
I will not force you. Anyone that wants to stay on  Earth shall stay.
강요하지는 않겠어
지구에 남고싶은 사람은 남아라
We'll join at 6 AM. Until then, you're free to do whatever you want.
집합은 내일 아침 6시
그 때까지는 자유 행동으로 한다
Dismissed!
이상!
Going to Space is definitely not a good idea. You guys don't know a thing.
역시 우주에 나간다는 건 무리야
너희들은 아무것도 몰라
That's right.
그래…
We know nothing.
우리는 아무것도 몰라
If you know, then why?
그런데 어째서?
We can go because we don't know.
모르기 때문에 갈 수 있는 거야
No matter how dangerous it is...
그게 아무리 위험하다고 해도…
This is youth!
이게 청춘이다!
That is Dagwon.
그게 다그온…
Maybe Brave Seijin knew from the very beginning.
브레이브 성인은 처음부터…?
I wonder.
과연 어떨까?
It might be that we don't want to think about anything at all.
단지 우리는 아무것도 생각하기 싫은 것 뿐일지도 몰라
It feels like something En would say!
왠지 엔과 대화하는 것 같아
Hey, don't treat me like him!
에, 아, 아니… 그런 녀석이랑 같은 취급하지마!
Sorry to call you, principal.
불러내서 죄송합니다
교장 선생님
Why did you call me?
무슨 일인가?
I want to ask you to take care of this woman for a while.
당분간 이 여성을 돌봐 주셨으면 합니다
Kai, I'll go too...
카이, 나도 함께…
You're wounded. We cannot take you with us.
넌 부상자야
데리고 갈 순 없어
Alright. I will take care of her.
좋네, 돌봐 주겠네
Thank you so much!
감사합니다!
-What's your name?
-It's Luna.
-이름은?
-루나라고 합니다
Luna, don't worry about it anymore.
루나, 뒷일은 걱정하지마
Principal will surely manage to help you.
교장 선생님이라면 반드시 힘이 되어주실 거야
Erika! I'm here!
에리카~ 여기야~
Erika, you're the best among all the girlfriends I have!
역시 수많은 여자친구 중에서도 에리카가 제일이야
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
Sawamura, you have guts to meet me again after I dumped you.
전에 나한테 호되게 차인 사와무라 군?
I'm beaten!
곤란한걸~
Actually, I am going for a trip for a while.
사실 나, 잠시 여행을 떠나게 됐어
Oh, is that so?
아, 그래…?
If so, come back after becoming a more trustworthy man.
그럼 조금은 믿음직한 남자가 돼서 돌아오렴
Yeah, will do.
그래, 그럴 생각이야
When I come back, will you be my girlfriend?
돌아오면… 돌아오면 나랑 사귀지 않을래?
Huh?!
뭐?!
Please! That's my wish of the life!
어때? 내 일생의 소원이야
Erika...
에리카…
Alright. Okay.
알았어 알았어
Well, I'll think about it.
뭐, 생각해 볼게
Yay! Yay!
앗싸~ 앗싸~
You stalker!
이 얼간이 녀석!
How are you doing?
몸 상태는 어때?
I'm doing great!
응, 아주 좋아
I'm not getting tired even after a stroll.
산책해도 몸이 안좋아지거나 하지 않아
I see.
그렇구나…
What's wrong, brother? You look weird today.
왜 그래, 오빠?
왠지 이상해
You do look tired. Did you catch cold?
기운이 없네
감기 걸린 거 아니야?
Seems that you don't have a fever.
열은 없는 것 같네
It's just your imagination.
기분 탓이겠지
-Really?
-Yeah.
-정말?
-그래
Right. Would you like to climb a mountain together?
맞다, 나중에 둘이서 산에 갈까?
That will definitely come true.
그거, 꼭 이루어질 거야
Hm? Did you make a drawing again?
음? 또 그림을 그린 거야?
Yes. I was going to a mountain with brother in today's dream.
응, 오늘 아침에 본 꿈에 오빠랑 나랑 산을 오르고 있었어
It will become true!
분명 진짜겠지?
Right.
그래
To me, it's now the best present.
지금의 오빠에겐 최고의 선물이구나
Hello?
Kazamatsuri?
카자마츠리 군?
You're nearby?!
근처에 와 있다고?!
No way!
말도 안돼!
Kazamatsuri!
카자마츠리 군~
You're really Kazamatsuri!
진짜 카자마츠리 군이네
Why are you here? I can't believe my eyes!
어떻게 된 거야?
믿겨지질 않아
I was just going nearby.
우연히 근처를 지나가게 됐어
What are you talking about? You're in Australia! There's no way you were just going nearby.
무슨 소리야 여긴 오스트레일리아라구
우연히 지나갈 리가 없잖아
Ah, right.
아, 그렇구나
Kazamatsuri, you had a mysterious side in the past.
카자마츠리 군은 예전부터 조금 신비한 면이 있었지
But by looking at your face, somehow I forgot everything that I hate.
그치만 카자마츠리 군을 얼굴을 보고 있으니까 왠지 싫은 것들이 전부 날아갔어
Did something happen?
무슨 일 있었어?
No, it's alright now.
아니, 이제 괜찮아
I guess you had many things going on.
이쪽에도 이런저런 일이 있지?
Yeah, many things. It really is something.
응, 이런저런 일이 있어 정말 큰일이라니까
Don't you feel suspicious of me?
절 의심하지 않으십니까?
You're not asking the reason I'm injured.
제가 다친 이유라든가 물어보지 않으시는군요
You're injured, but you're alive. That's all I have to know.
다쳤지만 자네는 살아있네 그럼 된 게야
Is that so?
그런 겁니까?
Did you know Hirose for a long time?
히로세와는 오랫동안 알고 지냈나?
No, that isn't it, but I always feel grateful to him.
아니오, 그렇지는 않습니다만 그에게는 무척 감사하고 있습니다
I always trust my students. Of course, Hirose too.
나는 말이지 나의 학생을 신뢰하고 있네 물론 히로세도 마찬가지네
Thus, as Hirose asked me to take care of you, I have no reason to have doubts about you.
그러니 히로세가 자네를 내게 부탁한 이상 자네를 결코 의심하거나 하지 않아
Why doesn't Ms. Luna try trusting him carefully?
루나 양도 그를 신중히 믿어보는 게 어떤가?
Yes.
네!
Dagwon! I brought this as you said!
다그온! 말한대로 가지고 왔어
Then, I'll allow you to take a souvenir picture of Power Dagwon!
그럼 가쿠에게 파워 다그온의 기념사진을 찍게 해 주마
Really?!
오오~ 정말?!
Yeah! Today is the special service day!
그래, 오늘은 스페셜 서비스 데이다!
If you keep being a good kid, Dagwon will keep looking at you children.
착하게 지내면 말이지 다그온은 너희들을 지켜보고 있다구
Strength Fusion!
강력합체
(剛力合體)
Power Dagwon!
파워 다그온
Alright, let's go.
좋아, 다 됐어
You're too big to take a picture!
너무 커서 전혀 못 찍겠어
I should step back more.
좀 더 떨어져야겠어
Now it works!
겨우 들어갔다!
-Then I'll take one!
-Sure!
-그럼 찍을게
-그래!
Awesome!
굉장해!
This picture will be my number one treasure!
이 사진, 내 보물 1호로 삼을 거야
Hey, wouldn't you tell us?
이봐, 슬슬 가르쳐줘
-Tell what?
-The true identity of Dagwon.
-뭘?
-다그온의 정체 말이야
-I'll let you know soon.
-It's a promise!
-조만간 가르쳐 줄게
-꼭이야!
Finally we're going to Space with this guy.
마침내 이녀석을 조종해서 우주로 가는구나
Oh, right. I should go buy some food.
아아… 맞다 식량을 구입하러 나가야지
Alright! I'll do my best to make food everyone will like in Space!
좋았어! 우주에선 실력을 발휘해서 맛있는 걸 만들자!
Ouch...
에고 아퍼…
No time for this.
이러고 있을 때가 아니지
So busy~
바쁘다 바뻐~
It'll be a boring journey to Earth.
지구에 도착하기까진 너무 지루한걸
Brother, do you know something fun?
형, 뭐 재밌는 거 없을까?
Why don't we drop Bomber Seijin who's in solitary confinement to the Earth first?
독방에 가둬둔 봄버 성인을 한발 먼저 지구에 떨구는 건 어떨까?
Bomber Seijin? That dangerous guy?
봄버 성인?
그 위험한 녀석?
Right. Wouldn't you think it'll be interesting as our declaration of war?
그래, 우리 선전 포고로써 정말 재밌을 거라 생각 안하나?
Are you finally going to let me explode?
드디어 날 폭발시켜주는 거야?
Wait! You're exploding on Earth!
기다려! 네가 폭발하는 건 지구다!
Earth?
지구?
지구…
Earth Explosion! Earth Explosion! Earth Explosion! Earth Explosion!
지구 폭발! 지구 폭발!
Hey stop that! You're noisy as heck!
에에이, 그만두지 못해?! 시끄러 죽겠다!
Hurry up and get him out of here!
어서 이녀석을 내보내라!
I wanna explode soon...
얼른… 얼른 폭발하고 싶어
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Original Korean Subtitles by Jaebari (재바리)
Translated to English by Subdivers
Checked by Great Exkaiser103
자막 원본(번역): 재바리
수정: Subdivers
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Huh? This isn't good.
어레레?
이거 심각한걸
Yo, occult girl.
여어, 오컬트 소녀
I guess your occult play is now over!
아아, 이걸로 겨우 오컬트 놀이도 끝이구만
What are you talking about? Such things won't make my supernatural Research Club disappear!
무슨 소리야 이런 일로 초상현상 연구회는 사라지지 않아
I know that some kind of unknown forces are trying to interrupt my research.
이것도 분명 어떤 미지의 힘이 내 연구를 방해하려고 하는 거야
Yeah, sure.
이봐…
내 연구를 방해하려고 하는 거야 이봐…
Oh, right. I'm here to pay you back the money I borrowed.
아, 맞다 나, 너한테 꾼 돈 갚으려고 왔어
Lies! I guess you're up to something to say a lie like that?
거짓말?! 그런 소리나 해대고… 또 무슨 일 꾸미고 있는 거지?
N- no! I just have to go to Space with my friends.
아, 아니야! 내일 애들이랑 우주로 가게 돼서 말이야
Interest not included.
이자는 안 붙어 있지만…
I don't need it.
필요없어…
It's not like you.
너답지 않아
You're like that after I finally managed to rake up?
뭐야… 모처럼 긁어모아 왔구만
Are you going to come back?
돌아올 거지?
Of course. When the battle is over, I'll come back.
그거야 뭐 싸움이 끝나면 돌아올 거야
-Absolutely?
-Yeah, absolutely.
-확실해?
-그래, 확실해
-How long will it take?
-I don't know well, but probably 4 or 5 days?
-언제 돌아올 거야?
-확실하진 않지만 4,5일 쯤 걸리겠지
Then pay me the debt when you're back.
그럼 빌린 돈은 돌아와서 갚아
You just told me that you don't need it!
좀전엔 필요없다며?
Let's decide the time and place!
시간과 장소도 정하자!
Let's see... Next week on Saturday, at noon!
그러니까… 다음주 토요일 낮 12시
The place will be... Ah.
장소는… 그래
In front of the bank with a big clock near Sankai bridge.
산카이 다리 근처에 있는 대형 시계가 있는 은행 앞
And the last one... are cup ramens that En senpai likes!
그러니까… 남은 건 엔 선배가 좋아하는 컵라면이다!
Why do you fight?
너는 왜 싸우는 거야?
That's because I'm a Dagwon?
그건… 다그온이니까
Because you're a Dagwon? Then, what do you fight for?
다그온이니까라니… 뭘 위해서 싸우는 거야?
What for?
뭘 위해서냐니…
To protect somebody?
누군가를 지키기 위해?
-Not likely.
-Do you have anybody you like?
-별로…
-좋아하는 애… 없어?
What? Do you even have one?
뭐야, 넌 있어?
Even for me, I do have someone I like.
아무리 나라고 해도 좋아하는 사람 정도는 있다구
Ms. Maria, please accept my feelings as of today!
마리아 씨 오늘이야말로 제 마음을 받아주십시오!
I'll... I'll...!
저는… 저는…!
Ms. Maria? And En, too?
마리아 씨?
거기에 엔까지
But hey, I guess that the one you'll like will probably be a monster or something.
하지만 말이야 하필이면 네가 좋아하는 녀석이니까 말이지 어차피 도깨비 같은 거겠지
Yeah, probably. I was careless.
뭐, 그렇지
나도 주의가 부족했어
Right! When you pay me the debt on Saturday, buy me a meal.
맞아! 토요일에 돈 갚는 김에 밥도 사줘
-And movies and karaoke too!
-You're a shameless fellow.
-그리고나서 영화랑 노래방도!
-뻔뻔하기는…
Ms. Maria...
마리아 씨…
Then see you.
그럼, 난 이만 갈게
Oh, right.
아, 맞다
Tell that monster I'll knock it out when I come back, so wait 'till then!
그 도깨비한테 말해 둬 내가 돌아오면 날려버릴테니까 그때까지 기다리라고 말이야
Hmph, do you think I will? It's a precious test subject!
흥, 아깝게시리 소중한 연구재료라구
I wouldn't do that!
그렇게는 못하지
Later.
그럼…
Th- that's how it was!
그, 그랬단 말인가!
Lian, we're finally fighting against Sargasso.
라이안 마침내 사르갓소와 대결하게 됐어
I'll do my best to take down all the bad aliens!
나쁜 우주인을 해치우기 위해 나, 힘낼 거야
Ms. Maria!
마리아 씨~
Good morning.
안녕하세요
I see that not everyone's here yet.
아직 모두 모이지 않았군요
Huh?
어레?
Geki, what's wrong? Your eyes are red.
게키, 왜 그래요?
눈이 빨개요
Shut up.
시끄러
If you care about him, you're going to be tired.
이녀석을 신경쓰면 이쪽이 피곤해져
Don't worry.
신경쓰지마
But...
그치만…
Don't mind him.
상관하지마
Rai, prepare for departure.
라이, 슬슬 출발 준비 부탁해
Yes, sir.
네
Activate Dag Base via spiritual wave!
정신파에 의한 다그 베이스 기동!
Huh? I thought I'd be the first one to be here!
어레, 내가 일등일 줄 알았는데
How was Australia?
오스트레일리아는 어떻더냐?
You followed me?!
뒤를 밟았어요?!
Idiot! Your face says so!
바보놈아
얼굴 보면 다 안다
Weren't you going to die from happiness?
나참, 좋아 죽을라는구만
I don't want to hear that from you.
신에게 그런 소리 듣기 싫어요
It's 6'o clock. Let's launch, Rai.
6시다
발진하자, 라이
But En senpai isn't here yet.
그치만 아직 엔 선배가 안 왔어요
It's over 6'o clock. As I said yesterday, anyone who's not here will be treated as ones who are not going to participate.
6시가 넘었어 어제 말한대로 오지 않은 자는 참가할 의지가 없는 간주
We'll leave him!
두고 간다!
-Let's wait for a bit.
-Yeah, let's wait, Kai.
-조금만 기다려보는 게 어때?
-그래 조금만 기다리자, 카이
No, there's no need to wait.
아니, 기다릴 필요 없어
En is better off staying on Earth with Ms. Maria.
엔 녀석은 마리아 씨와 함께 지구에 남는 게 최고야
Ms. Maria!
마리아 씨~
What are you talking about, Geki?!
무슨 소립니까, 게키?!
Without En, Dagwon's ability can't be fully demonstrated!
엔이 없으면 다그온의 실력을 발휘할 수 없잖아
Ms. Maria!
마리아 씨~
Hey, sorry, sorry!
여어, 미안 미안
I overslept.
그만 늦잠을 자 버려서 말이야
En! I thought you wouldn't be here at all!
엔! 틀림없이 안 올 줄로만…
En, you're late, even in this situation?!
엔, 이런 때에까지 지각이냐!
Don't be so stiff! Let's go lightly!
딱딱한 소리 말라구 맘편하게 가자구
You haven't changed a bit.
정말 변함없는 녀석이군
Dag Base - ascending.
다그 베이스
상승합니다
Dag Base - aircraft carrier mode.
다그 베이스
항모 모드
Transformation complete.
변형 완료 파이어 점보 및 선더 셔틀은
변형 완료
Fire Jumbo and Thunder Shuttle will operate in automatic mode.
파이어 점보 및 선더 셔틀은 자동 조종으로 전환합니다
-What's wrong?
-Big problem!
무슨 일이야?! 큰일입니다!
A big object is heading this way!
어떤 거대한 물체가 이쪽으로 향하고 있습니다
What's that?!
뭐야, 저건?!
Soon! In no time, I can explode!
이제 곧이다! 이제 곧 폭발할 수 있어!
That's... Bomber Seijin!
이건… 봄버 성인?!
Bomber Seijin?
봄버 성인?
Right! It's a bomb type alien with the power of easily blowing up a city or two!
그렇습니다! 폭탄형의 우주인으로 도시 하나둘은 간단히 날려버릴 만한 위력이 있습니다
The Warugaia Brothers must be behind this.
와르가이아 형제의 짓인가!
En!
엔!
Leave it to me!
나한테 맡겨 두라구
Strength Fusion!
강력합체
(剛力合體)
Power Dagwon!
파워 다그온
Earth Explosion! Earth Explosion!
지구 폭발! 지구 폭발!
Infinity Cannon!
무한포(無限砲)!
Target Lock!
타깃 록(TARGET LOCK)!
Set on!
세트 온(SET ON)!
Explode! Explode!
폭발! 폭발!
Fire!
발사(FIRE)!
Explode!
폭발---!
En!
엔---!
Understood, everyone?
모두 알겠지?
This journey will be a difficult one.
이번 여행은 상당히 힘들 거야
Kai senpai...
카이 선배…
Are you prepared for this?
각오는 되어 있겠지?!
I told you not to be stiff, Kai!
딱딱하게 굴지 말자니까, 카이
En...
엔…
We are Dagwon!
우리는 다그온이잖아
That's right! We're Dagwon after all!
그래, 우리는 다그온이라구
That's right.
그런 거지
It'll be alright.
괜찮습니다
Erika's waiting for me!
에리카가 기다리고 있어서 말이지
Alright. Brave Dagwon! Takeoff for Sargasso!
좋아, 용자 다그온! 사르갓소를 향해 발진!
The sun suddenly called me
태양이 갑작스레 나를 불러내서
taiyou ga fui ni ore wo izanau
To come to the blue sea
푸르게 비치는 바다로 만나러 갔지
aoku sukitooru umi ni ai ni kita
The ripples are coming and going
밀려왔다 돌아가는 잔물결
yosete wa kaesu sazanami
An endless melody
멈추지 않는 멜로디
tomaru koto nai MELODY
To keep that shape for eternity
그 모습을 영원히 유지할 수 있도록
sono sugata towa ni tsunagu you ni
I'll follow the fate of the dream
꿈의 행방을 뒤쫓아 갈 거야
oikakete yuku yo yume no yukue
Sparkling far away
멀리서 반짝이던
tooku kirameita
A Prism in the Wind
바람 속의 프리즘
kaze no naka no PRISM
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Preview for Next Episode
용자지령
다그온
차회예고
All the remaining aliens came to attack!
남은 모든 우주인이 총공격을 걸어왔어!
Alright! Shadow Dagwon and Super Liner Dagwon will get rid of them!
좋았어! 섀도우 다그온과 슈퍼 라이너 다그온은 그녀석들을 요격해줘
Sure! But this was a trap, after all!
알았어! 하지만 이건 함정이었어!
Moreover, Gedo invaded Dag Base!
게도가 다그 베이스 내에 침입했어!
Damn! Rai and I cannot stop him by ourselves!
젠장, 나와 라이만으론 저지할 수 없어!
What should we do? Dag Base will be destroyed at this rate!
어떻게 하지? 이대로는 다그 베이스가 파괴당하고 말아!
Next time on Yuusha Shirei Dagwon! Offense-and-Defense! Dag Base
다음회 용자지령 다그온
공방! 다그 베이스
At that moment, he came back!
그 순간, 그녀석이 돌아왔다!
Offense-and-Defense!  Dag Base
공방! 다그 베이스